Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Karayel! Come on!
Osman got down from the horse.
The horse went this way.
Useless!
What kind of a scout are you?
I can't bear foolishness.
He wants us to scatter.
If we can't find Osman,
Balgay will kill us all!
Let's go!
Kongar!
Its time for you to either
return to your roots...
... or...
... its time for you to die.
Running away! He's running away!
He's running away!
He's running away, my Gündüz!
We can't catch up without horses,
Bamsı Bey.
You red rat!
Son! Sofia is definitely involved in this.
Since Saltuk also came, someone from
the Tent is also involved, Bamsı Bey.
Then all the signs lead to Dündar.
What if Dündar is working with Alişar?
My uncle was with us.
He wouldn't have done it.
Son. What if he came to us
so someone else could do it?
What if all the autocracy was for this?
My Gündüz! He has a lot of
men in the Tent too!
Son! Don't give yourself up
to your emotions.
Don't you do it, son.
We'll figure this out, Bamsı Bey.
We'll figure it out.
Let's just pray that Zorba stays alive.
Let's go.
Kongar is still after me. You must
convince him before its too late.
I have completed your order.
Here is the proof that Balgay bought
Kongar, my brother Göktuğ...
... from the slave market.
Your brother Göktuğ will also
see Balgay's real face.
What was hidden is now evident.
Even though he is my brother
Göktuğ either believes us ...
... or faces the consequences.
Instead of a traitor brother...
... I'd rather have a dead brother.
Praise be! Karayel!
My heart, my soul.
So, you went to get herbs with
the cart, Zöhre Hatun.
Right before your daughter
was going to marry.
If something happens to Osman's legacy...
... I will show mercy to none of you.
My lovely daughters!
Demirci Bey's valiant Alps!
The sledge is here. Prepare it.
You're on your own from now on.
The person you're going to
deliver the girl to...
... will be waiting for you
by the Cehennem Creek.
Let's go. We don't have much time.
- Hope no one saw a thing.
- No, Zöhre Hatun. No.
What is it, Burçin?
You're shaking like a leaf.
I say no one saw us.
But what if someone did?
What if people find out?
If we were afraid of people finding out...
... we wouldn't have moved an inch.
People will eventually find out.
Don't you get it?
You have completed the duty
our Martyr son Aybars left unfinished.
We do what we do for the future
of Kayı and the future of our children.
Otherwise, why would we have
anything to do with this poor lady?
What we want is Dündar Bey
to get back the throne he deserves...
... and bring order once again.
If we have to give up our lives for
this cause, we will!
Relax. You did the right thing.
I got your back.
Let's go.
We went to get gather herbs. The cart is
loaded. If someone asks, we aren't lying.
Now it's obvious that you're
Dündar Bey's daughter, my Aygül.
- My smart daughter. Do you have the bell?
- I do, mother.
They...
... will be waiting for you
at the rocky side of the creek.
Ring this bell when you get close.
After you hear the response,
you'll find them. Go.
Good luck. May Allah protect you.
Now tell me!
Who killed Batur?
- Batur--
- Yes?
The one who killed Batur--
He didn't live long enough.
He died, poor thing.
My Gündüz! One died. Let's keep
the other one alive. Relax, son.
Bamsı Bey!
We'll take this Saltuk
to my uncle's side.
We'll see if he knew about
the betrayal or not.
We will, son. We will. Just relax.
Relax, my Gündüz.
Geyhatu is playing a wicked game.
He is in an alliance with a dark
league inside Byzantium.
This organization's name is
Monks of Margaret.
They are the ones who sent
Yannis and Sofia after us.
Through this organization,
Geyhatu wants to...
... put someone he's collaborating with
to the throne of Byzantine.
The only thing we can do
to find this person...
... and prevent a possible
Turk massacre in these lands...
... is to attack them
when they get together.
What is your order, my Bey?
We can cut them all.
No doubt, Konur brother.
But...
You won't come.
I will go.
My Bey, we can't leave you alone
in such a dangerous duty.
That's the order, Boran brother.
You won't come, I said.
You will go to the Tent, to my brother.
And you will take care of Kongar.
Besides...
Who said I was alone?
In this important duty...
... I too have a companion.
Tell us, my Bey.
Who is this valiant
that will accompany you?
A warrior who dedicates
his life to his traditions.
Someone great enough
to seep into these Monks.
Everything in this world has a purpose.
Lightning strikes, thunder cracks.
Water runs, Turkish
mothers give birth to valiants.
Thank you, Konur brother.
But Geyhatu is aware of this valiant.
I worry that both his life
and his trick is in danger.
My duty is to stop Commander Böke,
who was sent by Geyhatu.
Böke is coming to reveal this valiant
who seeped into the Monks.
They are in the Dark Alley near
the Mount Monk.
They will meet here.
Mount Monk...
There it is, my Bey.
But be careful.
It's not our territory.
Don't you worry, Konur brother.
Our valiants are wolves!
And the lands we step on are our homes!
You will see.
The day will come...
... and the crescent will shine
upon these lands.
Allah willing, my Bey.
Allah willing.
We'll rest here.
We won't stop until the meeting.
Get up on the hill.
See if anyone is following us.
You look a little worried, Master Hiristo.
I'm full of joy since we
will be getting rid of the Turks.
But I'm afraid of the consequences
of working with Mongols.
And also of the new Emperor
after we get the current one down.
Is he going to be powerful enough
to treat the Turks the way they deserve?
- Are we sure?
- I know that he is ambitious.
He grew up with hatred towards Turks.
Merciless. Smart.
Who is he? Who is this person who is
kept hidden from me and all the Monks?
You will find out when we get together
with the other Monks, Master Hiristo.
Are we sure?
So you are the snake who poisoned us!
We won't let you work with the Mongols!
Kill him!
Burn in hell, Turk!
We'll be your hell.
Traitor!
We brought the baggage safe and sound.
It's your business now.
Dündar Bey did a good job.
Alişar Bey sends his regards.
- Goodbye.
- Thank you.
You'll do a lot of our work for us.
She's all exposed. Soldiers!
Put something over her.
Let's get out of here.
She'll catch up.
Isn't that Saltuk?
What did he do?
Put him in the caged tent.
Dündar...
Let's go ask uncle Marife, Bamsı Bey.
He could read Zorba's eyes.
Dündar...
Is it you behind this too?
What is it, Boran? Why are you alone?
Where is Osman?
My Bey is on duty.
He sent me here. Maybe I could help.
What duty is this, Boran?
What if he gets in trouble?
He told me to go, Bamsı Bey.
He'll tell you the rest himself.
My Bey's orders. I can't tell you.
Let's go, Bamsı Bey.
Gündüz! Bamsı Bey! Wait!
What is it, aunt? What happened?
My Gündüz. Princess Adelfa isn't here.
Bala went to look for her.
Boran! Get the Alps and look for her. Go!
Go, my valiant!
- Okay, my Bey!
- Go, quick!
My uncle is on dangerous waters, my Bey.
As we ignore everything he does,
he is getting more mad by the day.
You stay, aunt.
We'll go and talk to him.
You can't find him, my Gündüz. Dündar
Bey, Zöhre and Aygül are not in the Tent.
I don't know what they're up to.
But they have disappeared.
This Dündar is asking for it!
I don't like where this is going.
He'll return here eventually.
We should remain calm.
We'll stand up to him when he is here.
Let's see what he'll do
when we tell him that we have Saltuk.
For my father's sake, I say.
He is my uncle, I say.
But he still does his thing.
Pity.
- I shot Zorba as you ordered, father.
- Is he dead?
He's dead, father.
My mad lion!
Your father would die for you!
Did anyone saw or got suspicious?
No one saw me. But they caught Saltuk.
- That's not good.
- Saltuk's mouth is sealed shut, father.
No knife known to man can make him talk.
Hopefully, son. Hopefully.
I don't care if he tells
everything he knows.
Now that you're here, my back is
more straight, my hands are more powerful!
- Thank you, father.
- How is your mother Hazal Hatun doing?
Didn't she want to come? Did she
forget the routes?
She's a Bey's daughter, you know.
Obeys the traditions.
She won't move until you order
her to come.
But only I know the longing in her eyes.
She'll come, son. She will.
After we clean our path, she will come.
You're bad with each other because of me.
I've made a big mistake.
Are you still mad at me, father?
Big Tents have big problems, son.
You were right in your own way.
And so was I.
So was your mother who
said, "If my son is exiled, so am I."
My Bey. We've delivered Adelfa.
People of the Tent think that we're
still bad with each other.
Let it remain that way.
So we can play our game with ease.
Go to the Tent.
Use this hostility as a weapon.
Let them think that we
still hate each other.
So that they give something away.
I'll pay a visit to Alişar Bey.
As you order, father.
The spirit of Margaret took root.
- Forever!
- Forever.
Brother! What happened?
Master Dennis.
They killed master Dennis.
May God protect us!
Who did this to you, brother?
The Turks!
Hurry up! Let's take him to Master Tilsus.
This is the truth, I say to you.
It doesn't have life in it before it eats
humans' flesh and drinks humans' blood.
Those who eat my flesh and drink
my blood have eternal lives.
And I will bless them in my final days.
Because my flesh is genuine food,
my blood is a genuine drink.
Master Hiristo!
Where is Master Dennis?
- We were attacked, Tesius.
- Who did this?
The Turks!
- How many were they?
- There were more than 20 Turk warriors.
- Most of them died.
- Do they know where we are?
- No.
- How can you be so sure, Master Hiristo?
They tortured Master Dennis
to find out our meeting spot.
I found a way and killed him
so that he didn't suffer.
May Mother Mary forgive me.
May she forgive my sins.
Master Dennis was both
a mother and a father to me.
Master Tesius.
Believe me, you're safe here.
You did something great, Master Hiristo.
But we should still be careful.
Everyone to their positions!
Take your precautions. If there were no
traitors among us...
... it would be impossible for them
to know our meeting spot. Quick!
Quick, I said!
My mouth is bubbling from hunger.
Light a fire.
I will hunt.
Osman!
I'll find you eventually, Osman!
You can't find him unless he wants you to.
Where is Osman?
What are you doing here?
He's loyal to his alliance with Balgay.
Firstly, remember that.
And about me...
I'm looking for you.
Do you want to fight alone? Is that why
you walk so sneakily?
If I wanted to fight, we would
have done it by now.
I don't want to fight you.
I want you to learn the truth and
return to your roots.
I protect my roots.
I fight on a horse like a brave Mongol!
You even don't believe what you've said.
You think you are a Mongol.
You also believe the tales you
memorize.
You think I am still your brother.
Tales, huh?
Look at this.
Is it a tale as well?
What's this?
A document that shows you being bought
from a slave market by Balgay.
He hides the truth from you.
Take it!
See it with your own eyes.
Göktuğ.
Come here, my son.
Oh! I have the same thing on me.
Of course you have, son.
We have it on all of our soldiers.
Argh.
Father.
Konur.
Göktuğ.
Father!
- Father!
- Wake up.
Father!
These tyrants use our
brave men against us.
Pull yourself together.
Be yourself, Göktuğ.
Don't forget that everything
turns back to its roots.
Wolves to wolves.
Dogs to dogs.
The mad one is coming.
Don't give something away.
Leave this to me.
May it be easy.
If you think that's easy,
come and do it.
What's that?
Do you use cars to gather herbs now,
Zöhre?
You see it with your own eyes.
How could we carry all those things?
When you meet with any obstacle, you
know looking for a cure.
But you don't know how those ointments and
drugs are made.
Meeting with an obstacle isn't
something bad.
The soldiers of Tent are dying for the
prosperity of Tent.
If you feel offended doing this, don't do.
We'll do it with the help of Allah.
Tell me.
Did you see Bala Hatun?
We didn't see or hear anything,
Selcan Hatun.
You look like your mother over time.
What a pity!
Tell me, Zöhre.
Bala Hatun and our guest have disappeared.
If you know or hear anything, speak.
If you don't speak even if you know,
I'll cut your tongue and you can't...
...speak from that time.
Look me, Hatun.
When my daughter needs to get downry
ready, she is cleaning the herbs.
When we need to do preparation for
wedding, we're working in here.
What're you saying?
It's a pity of you!
Dündar Bey is not around for a long time.
Where is he?
Dündar Bey is in the grave of his son.
Does he need to get permission from you?
Those who are innocent can do whatever
they like.
We can't say anything.
But there is the shadow
of betrayal on you.
We'll surely follow.
We'll surely ask.
If you are that curious, have
him followed.
You are making me angry.
We're doing our business.
That's enough.
Enough!
Does it fit the dignity of ladies of
Kayıboyu to fight like this?
Bahadır.
Welcome, son.
Zöhre Hatun.
My mother, Selcan Hatun, tortured
Hazal Hatun.
She never liked us.
But Zöhre Hatun is married
with my Father.
Don't treat her like that.
This is not you.
Where is Hazal Hatun, my son?
Is she alright?
She is alright.
With the help of Allah, I hope she
will come here.
We hope we will enjoy the
happiness of reuniting again.
We hope that we will be together again.
I hope we will be, brother.
Welcome.
How nice of you to come.
Aygül, you are beautiful as moon,
my sister.
Wonderful!
Don't stay standing.
Let's go to the Tent.
Tell me what you've done till now.
You too come, Burçin Hatun.
One period closes one period opens.
There will be hard days for you, Zöhre.
May Allah help you.
Zorba died.
I sent Bahadır to Tent so that he can
complete something left uncompleted.
Did Bahadır come alone?
He is with his sister and mother.
In the Çobanoğulları land.
He waits for my order.
Çobanoğulları is a powerful seigniory.
I didn't know that you were relatives.
You're stronger from now on.
Now we should wait for
the arrival of Osman.
When he comes, we will create trouble
in Tent and get the the seigniory back.
Wouldn't it be better not wait for
the arrival of him, Alisar Bey?
It's not.
We'll finish this job at once.
We'll catch them in an unexpected time.
Everyone is on the alert.
When is the unexpected time?
There's the fortitude of death and
relaxedness of marriage, Dündar Bey.
No one will expect the beat at the
night of the marriage of me and Aygül.
Welcome, Commander Böke.
The big day has come, sir Tesius.
Thanks to Geyhatu.
Many cities will surrender without being
looted.
The Constantinople will be in the
order of Geyhatu.
If there hadn't been the Monks of Margaret,
too much blood would be spilt, Tesius.
Let me introduce them.
Monk Vanko.
Monk Teron.
Monk Hıristo.
We've prepared a meal for you.
Come on in.
We've learned that Hıristo is a traitor.
Look everywhere.
You look this way.
Hurry!
Okay.
Bala Hatun.
How nice to see you again.
Drop it!
Now!
Run!
This way!
Hurry!
Soldiers!
Hurry, fools!
Someone took the Princess!
We'll catch up to her later!
A son of Kayı like you will be with you.
How did you infiltrate?
Who is behind you?
Which power?
Faith.
It's no use.
He'll not speak.
Jesus save us.
Turks know our all plan.
We know every step and breath
you take, Tesius.
You won't reach your goal.
We need to go from here right now.
Give me the names of spies in
the palace, Tesius.
All here.
But there are some issues
we need to agree on.
We will agree certainly.
You have your spies among
all people of the emperor.
There's more than that, commander Böke.
We need to dethrone the emperor before
our move is disclosed.
Every minute counts.
When the Princess Adelfa marries
Geyhatu, we will take gifts to the palace.
Our soldiers who take gifts and your
spies will capture the palace with you.
That's very good.
What about him?
He must die.
His being alive is a big threat for us.
I'll do this job.
If that girl gets out alive from the
forest, you won't leave this forest alive.
Did you understand?
Come on!
Kill her.
I know.
I made life miserable for you back
in the days.
I must have hurt all of you.
If it's like that, know that a different
Bahadır has come back.
I want you to forget the
disappointments and old fights.
We certainly don't want to hold grudge
and fall apart.
You came.
Welcome.
I hope your arrival
will be useful of our reuniting.
Good luck with it.
I hope so, Gündüz Bey.
I hope so.
But I don't know if my father will
accept me to his Tent.
Firstly, I have to apologize.
Then I want us to be strong and united
altogether.
Of course we should be.
When people of Kayı unite,
they can do whatever they want.
They can wipe out enemies.
I'm happy for your arrival.
I'm happier for your
arrival with such kind words.
If we talk about your father,
you will make it up certainly.
It'll be okay.
It'll be fine.
It'll be okay certainly.
My brother Batur has gone.
But fortunately
our Allah didn't allow us to be alone.
My Batur.
You're irreplaceable, my son.
You're right, Aygül.
Another son...
...from our blood...
...only could relieve this pain.
Bahadır.
Let's get up if you like, my son.
Thank you, Zöhre Hatun.
Can I get your permission, Gündüz Bey?
Yes.
You just rest.
We can talk later.
Thank you.
But first,
I've some things to deal with.
Selcan aunt.
You' used to make very good bulghur rice.
I didn't forget that.
If that's what you want,
I'll do it certainly.
Thank you.
My uncle isn't around still.
I didn't want to cause disturbance
as Bahadır just has come.
I didn't ask.
But I'm not comfortable.
Zöhre is trying to not give anything away.
But a lie is not something secret.
We'll disclose it.
Did Dündar go to the grave of Batur
or not?
Did you sort it out, son?
Yes aunt, I sent an Alp.
We'll see.
We will, son.
Then, we can smash them.
We are tired of fighting with
the enemies inside us, anymore.
That's enough.
After you dethrone the emperor,
puppet emperor will use you Böke.
Then, they'll get rid of you
as soon as possible.
Not emperor.
Empress.
You even don't know this.
And you're trying to destroy
the friendship of us with Mongols.
Look at your situation.
An empress will save you, right?
If you knew Sofia, you wouldn't
speak to me like that.
Die Hıristo!
Not Hıristo.
The son of Süleyman Şah, Sungur.
The uncle of Osman Bey?
It seems you know Osman.
You can kill me today, Böke.
But our sprouting branches
will choke you.
May witches take your life.
Allah is eternal!
Are you okay?
Yes.
Can you tell me your real name?
The son of Süleyman Şah, Sungur Tekin.
Uncle.
Osman.
Wonderful!
Uncle.
For years... We thought that you died in
Mongolian War, alongside uncle Gündoğdu.
The flesh is mortal but the soul isn't.
Uncle.
May Allah bless your weapon with
sharpness, son.
I wanted to speak to you before iftar.
You saw me and lost your appetite.
You want to say what you want already,
don't you, Zöhre Hatun?
What's done is done, Bahadır.
We struggled a lot, then. It's true.
But now is not the time to fight.
If we understand and trust each other, we'll
surely see the benefit in the future.
What you say is very nice and true.
To be honest, I'm glad you think that way.
It's time for unity, Zöhre Hatun.
My father is in trouble.
He needs support.
I'm sad to hear about Batur.
My condolences.
In a way, I'm your son, too.
And if you are sincere...
I'll be the first one to run to you.
But first, we must help my father.
There is revenge to take,
and scores to settle.
-So, you know what happened?
-I do.
Of course, I do.
I'm already after them.
Saltuk is in prison-tent.
He is no good for my father.
Gündüz Bey is looking for clues.
Hopes for Saltuk's help.
But Saltuk is tough.
I don't think he'll say anything.
Now if you'll allow me.
I want to rest.
Than you, Bahadır.
What can I say...
I didn't know you as a levelheaded man.
Now you are here, welcome.
May Allah clear your path and give you
strenght.
Thank you.
I'm glad my brother Bahadır is here.
He is a support for my father.
A reinforcement to his power.
He is, yes...
There is more to it than just that.
Let's see what will we do when his mother
arrives.
Don't speak like that, mother.
We won't wrangle. We'll stay away and
it will be alright.
Let's get through these hard times.
What good will staying away can do?
Just wait and see what will she do
when she arrives. She is a fox.
No one can deal with her sneakiness.
When she arrives...
We need to look for our back.
Otherwise the snake can strike
at any chance.
Look what Dündar does while you
have so many problems already.
Actually, I should come to the tents with
you and beat him until--
Uncle.
Uncle Dündar has a good heart.
When he finds out the truth...
...he'll know where to stand, for sure.
For years, I've struggled to take over
these names.
I was ripped from my tents, my
loved ones and everything.
And now you have it.
You did it, uncle.
Thanks to you, now we'll
have balance policy with Mongols.
I wouldn't succeed without you.
Thank you.
Council of elders wants to give this
document to the Emperor.
They don't want to deal with Byzantine
while we have the trouble of Mongol.
If the Byzantine Emperor gets rid of
the trouble of Margaret monks...
...we'll be relieved, too.
The trouble of Byzantine stands before
us for centuries, Osman.
They should stand for a little longer,
uncle.
Until we get rid of the Mongols.
When I look into your eyes,
I see your father.
You are valiant just like him.
Clever, just like him.
Thank you.
Who will they have sat on the Byzantine
throne as an Emperor, uncle?
The council of elders waits for the answer
of this question.
There won't be an Emperor but an Empress.
I'm not surprized.
Sofia.
You know her?
I know her heart.
I will rip it soon.
Did you think you can run away from me...
...with that little brain of yours?
Do you think it will end by kidnapping
a poor Bala Hatun, or killing her?
We'll come with our veterans, saints...
...and make these lands a part of
the Islamic world.
Now I think about it...
...you are no good to me alive.
Bala Hatun, you are wounded.
I'm fine, Boran Alp. I'm fine.
Thank you. You arrived in time.
But Helen ran away.
She can't go far.
Alps will take you to the tents.
I'll track her down.
No. Princess Adelfa is under
Osman's protection.
We'll go together.
C'mon, c'mon.
I need to go to Constantinople before it's
too late. Don't tell anyone about me.
Just know that I'll return when my mission
ends.
Don't worry at all, uncle.
Inform me from the Constantinople
where you go as a monk.
I need to know about their intentions,
about the plots they run before us.
I'll need that information. Until we get
rid of Sofya...
...and conquer Kulucahisar.
You never stop, do you?
Just like your father.
In these lands that we take root...
..our branches will go all over the world.
It doesn't fit us to stop.
I won't leave you uninformed, Osman.
Don't worry.
Karayel!
O' passenger! What is your destination?
The holy cause.
May Allah accompany you.
Time is coming. If you'll allow us, we
want to rest a bit.
Sure.
Let's wait for iftar in here.
Yes, Fakir Zülfikar. What do we
have for iftar?
Thank Allah for giving it to us.
We have a bit of honey and some
bread.
Praise Allah who shows us the halal
on the ground...
...and the crescent on the sky.
We've seen another ramadan...
Is this from Kayseri, Zülfikar?
Yes, my Sheikh. One of our
friends, Ahi İlhan sent it.
-May he live long. May Allah bless him.
-Amin.
What a great food that is, isn't it?
For a handful honey, thousands of
bees...
...visit hundreds of thousands of
flowers.
You can't underrate it to ''just bees''.
Qur-an has the sura of Nahl.
Nahl means honey bee.
Honey bees have a sura named after them.
Especially when the tyranny of the
heathens were at peak.
It was such a tyranny...
...many Muslim ate the leaves of trees
to survive.
They ate every piece of leather after...
softening it under fire.
Children and elders starved to death.
The sound of crying mothers and children..
...echoed in the streets of Maqqa.
And then, holy words came.
Friends, there is no time for the lesson
of faith.
It comes on peace time and war time.
Oneness is the first and the lesson in
Islamic school.
''Be like bees'' says Allah.
''Work like bees''
''Stay pure like bees.''
''Produce like bees. And don't
ever stop.''
Muslims didn't stop.
All the pain they carried...
...turned to labour pain, with
the efforts of these Muslims.
A civilized had born from the
womb of Mecca.
Led by our prophet...
...Muslims who worked with the patience
of a bee...
...created things with the taste
of honey.
But polytheists didn't understand the
value of them.
Instead of tasting the honey they made,
they tried to ruin it.
It isn't easy to create.
It takes patience, effort and love.
Of course, there will be ungrateful
people who don't appreciate the honey.
Our cure is hidden in our trouble,
friends.
Just like how the honey is hidden in
flowers.
Save me, my Bey.
-Saltuk?
-They won't show me mercy.
What does it mean, Gündüz Bey?
Since when do you punish an aide
before asking the Bey.
When it's about treason,
being an aide doesn't help, Dündar Bey.
This snake poisoned you, too.
Pity.
This man killed Zorba when he was
about to name the killer of Batur.
What is his aim, uncle?
Speak.
Is it true, Saltuk?
Never, absolutely not, my Bey.
It's a lie.
A slander.
I was hunting. They accuse me because
they've seen me with a bow.
My purpose wasn't killing Zorba.
The arrow on his hand didn't touch Zorba..
..but Zorba was in the reach of the arrow.
Saltuk was caught. It was someone else
who did it.
One who killed Zorba, ran away.
But his secret will be revealed, too.
Now...
...you will tell us all about this.
Uncle.
No sign of her.
We let her go away.
At least, we rescued you from
their hands.
Praise Allah, Bala Hatun.
I don't know what would I tell my Bey.
Thank you, Boran Alp. But we also need
to take the Princess, too.
Otherwise, I'll be embarrassed to
Osman Bey.
He told me to look after her.
Bala Hatun, let's go to the tents.
We know where they are.
We won't leave the princess to them.
Shame on me.
Shame.
My Allah, what will I say to Osman?
These are hard times.
What happened shook
all our balances.
I give his food...
...I keep his leashes...
...when he makes a mistake...
...he is mine to punish.
Saltuk grew up with me.
He can't betray us.
Saltuk! Come here.
Get up.
Mah Allah bless you, my Bey.
Gündüz Bey doesn't have bad
intentions.
He is trying to find the murderer
of his nephew.
Don't you be his enemy.
Follow his orders exactly.
Of course, my Bey.
Very soon, Alişar Bey and my Aygül
will marry.
It's been a long while since Kayı tents
seen entertainment.
I've done my part as an uncle.
I invited you. The rest is up to you.
Aygül is your daughter, and our sister.
Of course, uncle. Of course.
Father.
Don't.
Don't even touch my shadow.
Stay away from me!
Father, I came to ask for forgiveness.
You just rest, Bahadır. We'll find a way
to soften my uncle's heart.
Will he forgive me?
What father can resist his son?
You should stay strong.
We couldn't save Adelfa, my Bey.
We checked the grave, my Bey.
The soil is dry.
So, my uncle didn't go to the graveyard.
Son, Dündar is behind this.
We should stop him right now.
If we do it before the wedding, things
will go crazy.
We are in between the devil and the
deep blue sea, Bamsı Bey.
The gazelle couldn't get rid of the
hunters.
With Princess Sofia's regards...
...Princess Adelfa is yours, Alişar Bey.
What about Princess Sofia?
Where is she?
Is she busy with other stuff?
Princess Sofia is working on our alliance,
Alişar Bey.
She will tell you.
When we are done with Kayı Tribe, I will
deliver Princess myself.
Then, in these lands, there will be no
Osman...
...and no Kayı Alps.
Melik.
Take Princess to the dungeon.
Let her rest there.
Your magnificence shakes the tribe
Osman Bey.
Our ancestors say "A horse is ridden by
a Turk."
Welcome, Bahadır.
- What's new?
- I missed it.
I long for here, Osman Bey
I am from Çobanoğulları from my mother's
side, but I belong to here.
Mother side is cool,
but the father side is main.
You are right.
Are you good with my uncle?
No, he is still angry with me.
However, even he couldn't stop me from
coming back here.
If he doesn't take me in, I will pitch a
tent and stay here.
I am not going anywhere.
I heard that he holds you responsible for
Batur's death.
My uncle can't see the truth.
The more humans get elder, the more
they do mistake, Osman Bey.
I said it in the first place, Osman would
love and protect Batur.
But, you know, people talk.
And my father believed.
- Eyvallah (thank you)
- However, I don't think it's you.
I trust you.
Don't think of me as just a person.
Count me as a weapon of yours to
use against the enemy.
I will walk with you.
We will have a lot of time to talk.
Take care of yourself.
Zöhre Hatun.
I know you are worried because Bahadır
is here.
You are right, he was naughty
when he was a kid.
He gave us a hard time with his
rebellious personality. But he changed.
- He changed a lot.
- He will grow up.
He will grow mature.
He will calm down.
However, these are not enough, my Bey.
He betrayed you.
He can...
You say a betrayer can betray again,
huh, Hatun?
If so, I shouldn't have forgiven anyone.
I should have punished everyone who
backdoored me.
Don't bother yourself.
Bahadır's arrival will give us power,
you will see.
We have been summoned, my Bey.
Dowery is in the tent.
Carry it to the carriage.
- My Aygül.
- My Bey father.
We have not smiled for a long time.
Finally, I will be granted with my
daughter's happiness.
Finally, we will be stronger and happier.
First this marriage, then our jobs...
And then, the throne.
We will have what we deserve one by one.
Bala Hatun.
Osman.
Look up, sunshine.
Look up so that I can see your
beautiful face.
I couldn't take care of your entrustment.
How can I look to your face?
Forgive me.
The ones who are to shame are wandering
around, why do you feel embarrassed?
Don't be sad, if there is a betrayer
inside, you can't stop it.
Even if you carried it in your waist,
they would still do what they did.
Don't be sad.
What are we going to do now, Osman?
How can we find the Princess?
Eeh, my Lord sent her to us.
If we are meant to, he will send her
to us again.
Everything happens for a reason, my Bala.
Everything is done by Allah.
What a nice speech of yours,
what a nice look of yours.
You refresh my heart like the water
flooding down to mountains.
May my Lord bless you, inshallah.
May He bless us all, my Bala.
Brother.
- Osman.
- What is up?
Zorba...
They killed him before he talks, right?
Of course, they did.
Betrayers betray.
That's enough, Osman.
We are sick of them.
That's enough, Bamsı Bey.
I tolerated him because he was my uncle,
from my blood.
I didn't try to kill him, but...
We will face them.
We will arrive there and face them.
Let's go!
Dündar Bey, may it be good, inshallah.
Eyvallah, eyvallah (thank you).
Osman is coming, my Bey.
Get in the position.
They may attack.
Where are you going, uncle?
None of your business, Osman.
This game is over.
You can't leave these tents alive.
I am the only one that you haven't
bleed yet, am I not?
Only me.
The games you played now
chained you down. It's time.
How many more lives do you want
to take from these tents, Osman?
Aybars is gone... Bohaç, Erkut, Kantoğlu
have passed away.
They killed my Batur, too.
How much more brave man should die
to satisfy you? Speak, how much?
If you say that ''Uncle, I'll stop after
your blood''...
Come at me, then, my nephew.
Come. Your uncle's blood is halal to you.
Come and hit me with your dark weapon.
So that your rage can end,
your madness can stop.
Father, what are you doing?
Don't meddle. It's between us.
Your blood, your life isn't my trouble,
uncle!
What bothers me is the reputation
of Kayı.
Osman... For the reputation of Kayı...
...I gave up on mine.
I've lost the title of Bey but I still
pledged to Gündüz.
I supported him as long as our tents
stay safe.
Isn't it true, Bamsı Bey?
Speak, Gündüz. Is there any lies in
my words?
Is there? Huh?
Haven't I?
So did I, uncle! I said many times that
Alişar isn't a friend.
What did you do? You took shelter
under him.
Like it wasn't enough, you gave him
Aygül.
Commander Böke.
What's happening, Commander Böke?
Where are your warriors?
Osman... He killed the monks of Margaret.
I said that Osman destroyed everything.
Don't you understand?
How?
How could he know where the Monks of
Margaret are?
Not just that. He knew everything!
Everything!
That I was coming, that why did
we meet. Everything!
Osman! Osman! I'll kill that dog!
You are late, Alişar Bey, late!
Your bannerlord. A tribe bey under you.
You couldn't manage to stop him.
When Geyhatu finds out about it...
...he'll make you pay.
Was I supposed to ask you who should
I give my daughter to, Osman?
Are you a common man, uncle?
How can you give a woman of Kayı...
...to a man who attacks our tents
at any chance...
...and try to sow discontent
among us?
Ahh, Osman.
You don't know how to behave...
If you thought so much of Aygül...
...why did you say no, when I told you
to marry her?
I took you by my side, told you to take
my daughter, so we could be closer...
What did you do? Huh?
What did you do?
Gündüz, do you hear what your
brother says?
You accused in vain.
Failed to prove.
Now you want to hit me by my daughter?
Do you think I gave her by force?
Here, her face is here. Since your
secret is revealed...
...ask to her face...
...does she want this marriage or not?
Uncle!
Are these issues meant to be
spoken in public?
Osman.
We came here to call out.
What did you turn it into?
Keep it short.
I have spoken.
Know that I won't let Aygül marry Alişar.
Please contact turkision@gmail.com
for any inquiries